yourchildlearns.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy - Owl & Mouse Educational Software

|    

•  Software for learning letters of the alphabet, learning phonics and letter sounds, and learning to read.  
•  Online US maps, world maps, map of Europe, puzzle maps of the US, Europe, Africa, Asia and many more.  
•  Build a medieval castle and make a coat of arms – all free! 

* * *  

  |   |    

     The privacy and security of visitors our website is very  important to Owl and Mouse Educational Software.  Owl and Mouse collects no information from visitors and we do not use ‘cookies’.

     At Owl and Mouse, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit yourchildlearns.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We do not retain any information and never sell your personal information to third parties.

     Site logs are not retained or shared by yourchildlearns.com. They are only used to generate aggregated statistics—such as the page hits or the time of day users visit our site.  We use Google Analytics –you can see their privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/).

     We use third party advertisements on Owl and Mouse to support our site so that all our content can be free.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).  Google advertising privacy policy is [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/).

     You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites

     The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

     Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to display ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website.  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables Google and its partners to display ads to users based on their visit to our site, or other sites on the Internet, or both.

     Users may opt out of the use of the DART by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).   
  
* * *

We welcome all comments on your and your children's experience with our maps and software.  Any additional learning ideas will be added to our pages (with credit to you) for others to enjoy.

E-Mail us at: [Owl and Mouse](mailto:owlmouse@yourchildlearns.com)

Privacy Policy   -   Terms of Service

All Material Copyright 1998-2011 Owl and Mouse Educational Software

All pages and downloadable software may be freely used for individual and classroom instruction but may not be sold or redistributed.
